

# **AMIT PANDEY**

# YOGA MASTER 瑜伽大師

To inspire people through the practice of yoga to connect with their own personal wisdom healing abilities and expansive potential, at the same time secure a role of Yoga master and possess professional experience in the field of yog.

通過瑜伽練習激發人們與個人智慧治愈能力和擴展潛能的聯繫,同時獲得 瑜伽大師的角色並擁有瑜伽領域的專業經驗。

### **CONTACT** 联系方式

+91-9702-744-442

amit.pandey@yogintra.com

www.yogintra.com

amit020187

@yogintra

Diva, Thane, Mumbai 400612

## LANGUAGE 语言

Hindi 印地语 Chinese 中文 English 英文 Sanskrit 梵语

## INTEREST 爱好

Yoga 瑜伽 Swimming 游泳 Travel 旅行 Music 音乐

### PERSONAL DETAILS 个人资料

Father (父亲):- Hari Govind Pandey

Mother (母亲):- Mira Devi Pandey

Religion (宗教):- Hindu

Marital Status (婚姻状况):- Single

Date of Birth (出生日期):- 02-Jan-1987

#### SKILLS 技能

Multi Style of Yoga

多种瑜伽风格

\*\*\*

Knowledge teaching and design Yoga class

知识教学与设计瑜伽课 👚 👚

 $\star\star\star\star$ 

**Conduct Teacher Training Course** 

开展教师培训课程



Leadership Skill

领导能力



# EDUCATION 教育

### **CERTIFICATE COURSE IN YOGA**

瑜伽证书课程

2011 - 2012

Kaivalyadhama Mumbai 卡达姆孟买

#### **RYS200 YOGA ALLIANCE TTC**

瑜伽联盟教师培训课程

July - 2015

AATM Yogshala, Rishikesh 瑞诗凯诗

### **CERTIFICATE COURSE IN YOGA**

瑜伽证书课程

2014 - 2015

Kaivalyadhama Lonavala 克达姆罗纳瓦拉

#### **RYS500 YOGA ALLIANCE TTC**

瑜伽联盟教师培训课程

July - 2018

Vyasa Yoga Peeth, Rishikesh 瑞诗凯诗

## **RYS500 YOGA ALLIANCE TTC**

瑜伽联盟教师培训课程

October - 2018

Daneshe Yoga Vidyalaya, Mysore 迈索尔

## POST GRADUATE DIPLOMA IN YOGA

瑜伽研究生文凭

2021 - 2022

Maharishi Dayanand Yog Sansthan, Uttaraakhand 北阿坎德邦

# M.A IN YOGA (APPEARING)

瑜伽大师

2022 - 2023

Uttaraakhand Sanskrit University, Haridwar 北阿坎德邦梵语大学,哈里瓦

DOAP-GDY IN COMPUTER 办公自动化和出版文凭- G.D.Y.

2008 - 2009

RGCSM University RGCSM 大學

# WORK EXPERIENCE 工作经验

# Yoga Teacher 瑜伽老师

2012 - 2013

Worked in R.K.T College of Art's, Science & Commerce, Ulhasnagar Mumbai, there I teach to student in group to develop them mind growth, increase focus and develop physical strength.

在 R.K.T 艺术、科学与商业学院 (Ulhasnagar Mumbai) 工作,在那里我以小组形式教导学生,以发展他们的思维成长、增加注意力和增强体力。

## Yoga Teacher 瑜伽老师 2013 - 2014

Attending daily drop down Yoga class at MAA GANGA GUEST HOUSE Laxman Jhula, Rishikesh, there I teach daily drop in Foreigner & Indian class with different style as per them demand. 参加瑞诗凯诗 MAA GANGA GUEST HOUSE Laxman Jhula 的日常瑜伽课程,在那里我根据他们的需求教授不同风格的外国人和印度人课程。

# Yoga Teacher 瑜伽老师

2014 - 2015

Worked in YOG SUTRA FOUNDATION Laxman Jhula, Rishikesh, there I assisted with senior teacher daily drop in & TTC for Foreigner & Indian Student.

曾在 YOG SUTRA FOUNDATION Laxman Jhula, Rishikesh 工作,在那里我协助高级老师每天到访和为外国人和印度学生提供 TTC。

## Yoga Teacher 瑜伽老师 2015 - 2016

Worked in Raman Thyssen Shenyang, China, there I teach daily group classes also personal class.

在中国沉阳拉曼蒂森工作,在那里我每天教授小组课程和个人课程。

# Yoga Manager 瑜伽经理

2016 - 2020

Worked with LEO FITNESS Jiexiu, Shanxi, China, there was my responsibilities to make class schedule as per Student requirement, arrange classes as student demand and help teacher to grow business, recruit creative & responsible yoga teacher to help grow in business, conduct Teacher Training Course, attending daily group yoga class to let the student different verity of classes, also attended private yoga class who have Mental & physical disorder to heal them by yoga classes.

在中国山西省介休市LEO FITNESS工作,我的职责是根据学生的要求制定课程表,根据学生的需求安排课程并帮助老师发展业务,招聘有创意和负责任的瑜伽老师来帮助业务发展,进行教师培训当然,每天参加团体瑜伽课,让学员感受不同的课程真实性,也参加私人瑜伽课,让身心障碍的人通过瑜伽课来治愈他们

## Yoga Manager 瑜伽经理 2020 - 2023

I am founder YogIntra, in pandemic we started some online classes to help pandemic patient fight to survive life and we made it in India our platform become famous for Online Yoga Classes, Retreat & Teacher Training Course. from 2022 to till we are doing Retreat & Teacher Training world wide.

我是 YogIntra 的创始人,在大流行期间,我们开设了一些在线课程,以帮助大流行患者为生存而战,我们在印度使我们的平台以在线瑜伽课程、静修和教师培训课程而闻名。从 2022 年到直到我们在全球范围内开展务虚会和教师培训。

# Declaration (宣言)

"I hereby declare that the information giver above is true to the best of my knowledge & belief".

"我特此声明,据我所知和所信,上述信息提供者是真实的"。

Date (日期):-

Place (地方) :- Mumbai (孟買) Amit Kumar Pandey